Previously on JoJo's Bizarre Adventure!
I don't think I'm going to
be able to help you, folks.
It's been my job to repair rooftops
in Cairo for around 40 years now.
And I can't say that I've
ever seen a place like this.
And my daughter's condition is much worse.
At best, she has three or four days left.
I can almost feel it.
It's like Dio's right on top of us.
We should get moving.
We'll talk to everyone
here until we find him.
It's a real scorcher out here today.
I haven't had a shower in almost two days.
It's beginning to ruin my je ne Suzi Quee.
Huh?
Uh... Hmm.
What's the big idea, asshole?
You got some kind of problem with me?
I've got a problem with
where you're sitting!
A cocky foreigner like you has no business
sitting here pretending
to be some kind of beggar!
Don't you have a lick of common sense?
Who said that you could sit here, huh?
Ah, you must be a beggar
from a foreign land.
I know this isn't much
But I hope it helps.
Thanks, but
You back off pal.
This is my turf.
You poofy-haired blockhead
What's that supposed to hey hold a wrap?
Don't just sit there with your mouth agape
give that money to him immediately Hmm?
Oh, I get what's going
on here. He's a beggar.
You'll have to forgive my
friend's obliviousness.
He's not accustomed to
the rules of this city.
Why didn't you tell me you were
a beggar in the first place?
It's called having a shtick, you numbnut.
People around here know
me as a mute beggar.
There's something known as
a beggar's association here.
Beggars have their own
areas where they're paid
to do nothing but sit
around and beg all day.
While it may seem strange to us,
the rules they put in place help
keep everything running smoothly.
Get out.
Yes, and that exchange from
earlier has hurt my pride.
I wonder if I'd make more money by
disguising myself as a foreign beggar.
The hobos, they are a changin'.
Oh, by the way, I thought I
recognized you from somewhere.
If I'm not mistaken, you're
Avdol the fortune teller.
Way I hear it, you got
spooked and fled to Japan.
Apparently, someone was
looking to kill you.
I'd rather discuss us needing
a favor from the one who knows
everything there is to know about
this area you'll be well compensated.
It's imperative that we find this
building as quickly as possible.
We're running out of time.
I've done enough work for one day.
You gents have my word that I'll
find the mansion in three hours.
Just sit tight.
By the way, did anyone
see where Iggy ran off to?
I am never going to work with fire!
I am not going to die!
Start, I am not gonna die!
When the life is happening?
Changed the moment!
To be done, I will not continue.
I will continue to walk in the end.
I faced the last page.
Hear!
Oh, my God.
Naaah!
Come on.
That's the place all right.
Mission accomplished and
it only took two hours!
If it exists in this city you can
bet your ass I'll find it. Huh?
Iggy thought to himself.
So, that bird is a stand user, same as me.
Given that it offed that guy
with a giant block of ice,
it must be the guard around here.
It'll kill anyone who
approaches the mansion.
Which means that bird's next
target is probably gonna be me.
From early on,
the ancient Egyptians
recognized the prowess of
the noble falcon soaring
high above the Nile Valley.
They trained the bird
as a hunting partner.
And considered it a symbol of Horus?
guardian deity of the royal family.
The falcon's vision is able to spot
prey from several kilometers away.
Its oculus is forever
represented by the Eye of Horus,
an emblem of protection and royal power.
The falcon soaring through
the air is called Pet Shop.
It is the wielder of the
Stand Horus, God of the Sky.
Nervously, Iggy thought, Damn
it, this is just my luck.
Looks like I stumbled on Dio's mansion.
Why'd I have to find this place
instead of one of the others?
What's worse, that falcon can use its
stand to shoot giant chunks of ice.
It's like a super powered guard dog.
Actually, it's more like a guard bird.
Come on, you gotta be kidding me.
I couldn't care less about this Dio guy.
I got dragged here against my will,
Like some pet and forced to be
one of the Joestar's allies!
Like hell I'm gonna fight this thing.
All I want is a little Aranar.
A girl of my own.
Some place to settle down.
Fighting someone else's battle
isn't on my list of things to do.
Besides,
even if I were to throw down with Tweety
over there, what would I get in return?
There's no way I'm putting
my life on the line.
Time to bring out that
old dumb dog routine.
That bird brain will never
suspect them with those guys.
Those eyes, that's the thing about birds,
you can never tell what they're thinking!
I bet my stand could take him,
but then again, there's a reason I'm
making a fool out of myself here.
I've got nothing to do with
Jotaro and those other guys.
Go back to your mansion,
you feathered freak!
Huh? A bird?
What's with this bird?
Why isn't the damn thing moving?
No, it's too late!
I'm gonna run it over!
I've never seen anything
like that bird in my life.
How could it fly under a
car so low to the ground?
It didn't even try to
dodge out of the way.
It dove without giving
it a second thought.
Crazy bastard.
But it seems like the freaks
lost interest to me, for now.
Well, apparently,
it only goes on the offensive when people
try to make their way inside the mansion.
Even so,
if Jotaro and the others ever
end up finding this place,
they'll have a hell of
a time trying to get in.
Oh well, that's their
problem to deal with.
Butch! Tiny! Butch! Tiny!
Where'd you guys go?
Hey, you haven't seen my
dogs around, have you?
Their names are Butch and
Tiny, if that helps at all.
Get the hell out of my face.
I'm a dog, pal.
Even if I knew, it's
not like I could answer.
What are you, stupid?
Oh, no.
That collar looks like...
I was right.
It's Tiny's.
I don't understand.
Why is it under this gate?
And why is there blood on it?
Tiny and Butch?
Is he talking about those big dogs?
Tiny!
Butch!
What's that kid thinking?
If he tries going under the gate, he'll
have to face the wrath of that bird!
It'll murder him!
Tiny! Butch! Are you there?
Tiny! Butch!
I don't know why I'm getting so worked up.
If some human kid bites a
big one, it's not my problem.
Survival of the fittest, as they say.
The stupid die first, as do
people who act recklessly.
I'd rather stay out of
this, so... Goodbye, kid.
Tiny! Butch, come out! This isn't funny!
I'm here to take you home!
Holy...
Shiii!
Good grief.
I have a soft spot for kid
dog lovers lucky for him
I didn't want to get involved,
but it's up to me now!
He had finally revealed his stand,
confirming Pet Shop's suspicions about
Iggy's extraordinary canine abilities.
Bring it, Feather Boy!
I can't wait to rip you to shreds!
The Falcon is known
for its ability to dive
at speeds of over 300 kilometers per hour.
making it the fastest
animal on the planet.
Even at its trademark speed, the falcon
can spot its quarry with pinpoint accuracy.
The prey, once discovered, faces a violent
death by way of razor-sharp talons.
Huh? What the?
Did he just smirk at me?
I could have sworn I saw the
corners of its beak creep up.
But birds can't smile, can they?
Wait, what's going on here?
The air, it's getting colder.
Ice is coming out of the ground!
I'm such an idiot!
I was so focused on the bird, I didn't
realize my feet were frozen over.
My stance feet froze too!
Shit!
Icicles!
Come on, give it to me straight, Avdol.
Do you honestly believe that guy has
any chance of finding Dio's mansion?
I certainly hope so,
because if he can't find it,
there's no one left in this city who can.
No one knows Cairo's complex
maze of streets better than him.
Try and have some faith.
Faith is something I'm
quickly running out of.
We've been looking around this godforsaken
city for three days with no luck.
I highly doubt some beggar will
find the mansion in three hours.
You're starting to sound like
a broken record, Polnareff.
You could at least try
to keep a level head.
Listen up.
We're all on edge right now.
Until our friend gets back, all we
can do is try talking to the locals.
Oh, brother.
And to make matters worse,
we haven't seen Iggy all day.
Where the hell did that
stupid mutt run off to?
He better not be lost.
For as long as I've known him, Iggy's
always been somewhat of a loner.
So I'm sure he's just
wandering around somewhere,
killing time before coming back home.
I used to think all dogs lit up and
wagged their tails when they saw humans.
How'd we get stuck with that little cynic?
I managed to get away from it somehow!
It's Stan's ice attack took
the skin right off my paws!
Damn it!
I knew I should've let that
human kid fix his own problems!
It's Stan's power is nothing to sneeze at!
That was no ordinary ice!
And I bet he still has a few tricks!
I'd better get out of here
while the getting's good.
Talk about holding a grudge!
Iggy disappeared, but
where could he have gone?
Damn it.
That hurt.
The bastard doesn't hold anything back.
He's strong.
For a dumb bird.
This place reeks, but
it'll have to do for now.
We have to keep quiet and hide
out down here until he gives up.
What is this freaky bird's deal?
Hey!
Surprise!
Thought you had me, didn't you?
But what you killed was my
shape-shifting stand, the fool!
Yeah!
How do you like them apples, Featherbrain?
Might want to keep still.
Looks like you're losing
a lot of blood there.
But before this drags out any further,
you should probably know I don't give
a rat's ass about you or your master.
Deal?
What do you say we call this a draw?
You got a few good hits in
with those ice missiles.
So we're even. Right?
Wh-What the hell was that?
Who does this guy think he is, Bruce Lee?
Hey! Can't you hear?
I said I'll stay away
from your boss's mansion!
Let's stop this, okay?
That's what your skin looks like?
What am I going to do now?
You stopped your wound from
bleeding by freezing it?
What the hell? Ah!
Blast it!
Oh no, the exit's blocked with ice!
And more is coming this way!
Shit!
It's time to cover the whole tunnel!
I gotta find a way out of this death trap!
Ah!
No way you plucked off this exit, too!
Crap.
It's got me in its crosshairs.
This bird's insane!
This is more than sheer determination.
This creep's a frickin' killing machine!
And if it catches me,
it won't just kill me.
It'll leave me alive!
I'm alive!
What?
No, it's my ball!
I can't fret my pull-a-loose!
Thank you.
Can my luck get any worse?
That lousy fleabag.
That bird is pissing me off!
It didn't occur to me until a moment ago,
but a stand user is likely
to be guarding Dio's lair.
Either way you slice it, I don't have
much choice, so it's do or die time!